Under the glow of the silver moon, I find my heart in a tender tune.
Every step brings me close to you, every moment feels so true.
Soft is the night as it holds our song.
In your embraces where I belong, every glance is a sweet surprise.
I keep dancing in your eyes.
Round and round the wall fades away.
Love is the music and we will sway.
Hand in hand through the gentle sky, forever dancing.
In your eyes.
No time, no fear, just you and me spinning like waves on a timeless sea.
Every heart retails me, it's true, my forever begins with you.
Round and round the world fades away.
Love is the music and we will sway.
Hand in hand through the gentle sky, forever dancing.
In your eyes.
Round and round the wall fades away.